On Earth everyone can hear you scream.
Aliens vs Predator: Requiem is a action, science fiction,
thriller film directed by Colin Strause.
After a horrifying PredAlien crash-lands near a small Colorado town, killing everyone it encounters and
producing countless Alien offspring, a lone Predator arrives to "clean up" the infestation.
Dale, played by David Paetkau.
Tim, played by Sam Trammell.
Dallas Howard, played by Steven Pasquale.
Kelly O'Brien, played by Reiko Aylesworth.
Sheriff Eddie Morales, played by John Ortiz.
Ricky, played by Johnny Lewis.
Predator: Requiem (stylized on-screen as  AVPR: Aliens vs Predator - Requiem) is a 2007 American
science fiction action horror film that is the second installment in the Alien vs.
Predator franchise, and a sequel to Alien vs.
Predator (2004).
The film was directed by the Brothers Strause
from a screenplay by Shane Salerno.
Set immediately after the events of the previous film, the film begins with a Predator ship crashing into a forest outside of
Gunnison, Colorado, where an Alien-Predator hybrid known as the Predalien escapes and makes its way to the nearby small town.
Wolf, a skilled veteran "cleaner", is dispatched to kill the Predalien,
and the townspeople try to escape the ensuing carnage.
The film stars Steven Pasquale, Reiko Aylesworth, John
Ortiz, Johnny Lewis and Ariel Gade.
Predator: Requiem premiered on November 4, 2007, in Los Angeles.
It was released theatrically on December 25 in the United States.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics for its
poor lighting, editing, and lack of originality.
It grossed $130.2 million worldwide against a production budget of $40 million.
Plans for another sequel were abandoned, with further independent entries
in both franchises released in 2010 and 2012 respectively.
The film explores themes of predator, hybrid, colorado, national guard, morgue.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.